Funny in a new and frightening way!
Little Murders is a comedy, crime film directed by Alan Arkin.
A young nihilistic New Yorker copes with pervasive urban violence, obscene phone calls, rusty water pipes,
electrical blackouts, paranoia, and ethnic-racial conflict during a typical summer of the 1970s.
Alfred Chamberlain, played by Elliott Gould.
Patsy Newquist, played by Marcia Rodd.
Carol Newquist, played by Vincent Gardenia.
Marge Newquist, played by Elizabeth Wilson.
Kenny Newquist, played by Jon Korkes.
Mr. Chamberlain, played by John Randolph.
Little Murders is a 1971 American black comedy film directed by Alan Arkin, in his
feature film directorial debut, and starring Elliott Gould and Marcia Rodd.
Based on the stage play of the same name by Jules Feiffer, it is the story of a woman, Patsy Newquist (Rodd), who brings home her boyfriend, Alfred Chamberlain (Gould), to
meet her severely dysfunctional family amidst a series of random shootings, garbage strikes and electrical outages ravaging their New York City neighborhood.
The film explores themes of new york city, nihilism, parent
child relationship, photographer, dark comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.